Rockwell Kent papers 4079547
Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Series VI:Book Illustration
  - Melville, Herman
    - Moby Dick. New York, Random House, 1930.
      - p.141: ink and pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 20)
      - p.152: ink draft (Box 20)
      - p.165: pencil draft (Box 20)
      - p.248-lettering and layout: pencil draft (Box 20)
      - p.253: ink and pencil draft (Box 20)
      - p.265: pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 20)
      - p.307: pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 20)
      - p.419: pencil and ink draft (Box 20)
      - p.481: ink drafts, 2p. (Box 20)
      - p.674-lettering and layout: pencil draft (Box 20)
      - p.787: pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 20)
      - oversize ink sketch, 1p. (unpublished) (Mapcase 13V-F-05)
      - "Captain Ahab;" see: Advertising: The Lakeside Press (Chicago)
      - ink draft (preacher) (Box 20)
      - ink sketch (preacher) (Box 20)
      - ink drafts, 5p. (Box 20)
      - ink sketches, 8p. (Box 20)
      - pencil drafts, 17p. (Box 20)
      - proofs, 30p. (Box 20)
      - proofs-photostats, 11p. (Box 20)
      - lettering: pencil drafts, 4p. (Box 20)
      - oversize lettering: pencil draft (Mapcase 13V-F-05)
      - texts, lists, etc., 5p. (Box 20)
      - prospectus (Book of the Month Club): printed copy (Box 20)
      - sample pages: printed leaflet (Box 20)
      - clipping (ad) (Box 20)
    - Moby Dick:
      - cover design: ink and pencil drafts (Box 20)
      - cover design: oversize pencil drafts, 4p. (Mapcase 13V-F-05)
  - Nash, Ogden
    - Quartet for prosperous bastards. Privately printed, undated
      - printed copy with hand-colored illus., 2 l. (Box 20)
      - proof of illus. (printed in colors) (Box 20)
  - Norris, Charles G.
    - Seed. Garden City, NY, Doubleday Doran, 1930.
      - title-page illus.: pencil sketch (Box 20)
    - Zest. Garden City, NY, Doubleday Doran, 1933.
      - book jacket: pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 20)
  - Paramore, Edward J., Jr.
    - The ballad of Yukon Jake. New York, Coward-McCann, 1928.
      - "But, miles away, in Keokuk, Ia.;" ink sketch (Box 21)
      - "Then he rowed her ashore, with a broken oar;" ink sketch (Box 21)
  - Phillips Academy, Andover, Mass.
    - Yearbook:
      - [skier]: pencil sketch (Box 21)
  - Pierce, Waldo
    - Unser Kent. New York, privately printed by C[rosby], G[aige] & F[rederick] W[arde], 1928.
      - frontspiece: ink and pencil drafts (Box 21)
      - frontspiece: pencil draft (Box 21)
  - Powell, Lawrence Clark
    - Robinson Jeffers: the man and his work. Los Angeles, The Primavera Press, 1932
      - initial letters: ink sketches (Box 21)
      - prospectus: 2 printed copies (Box 21)
  - Prize poems 1913-1929. New York, Charles Boni, 1930.
    - cover design: pencil draft (Box 21)
    - cover design: proof (Box 21)
    - cover design (not used): pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 21)
  - Pushkin, Alexander
    - Gabriel. New York, Covici-Friede, 1929.
      - cover design (À): pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 21)
      - pencil drafts, 3p. (Box 21)
  - Quinn, Mike
    - The big strike. Olema, CA, Olema Pub. Co., 1949.
      - book jacket: pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 21)
  - Reitz, Deneys
    - Commando. New York, Boni, 1930.
      - cover design: watercolor sketch (Box 21)
  - Robinson, Selma
    - City child. New York, The Colophon, 1931.
      - frontspiece: proofs, 2p. (Box 21)
      - p.49: ink sketch (Box 21)
      - p.49: pencil and ink draft (Box 21)
      - prospectus: printed leaflet (Box 21)
  - Ruggles, Carl
    - Toys. (sheet music)
      - cover design: (Box 21)
      - pencil draft (Box 21)
  - Shakespeare, William
    - The complete works... [Limited De Luxe Ed.]
      - prospectus: printed leaflet (Box 21)
  - Shakespeare, William
    - The complete works ... Garden City, NY, Doubleday Doran, 1936.
      - book jacket: mock-up copy (Box 21)
      - proofs, 11p. (Box 21)
      - oversize proofs, 7p. (Mapcase 13V-F-05)
      - proof (black and red) (Box 21)
      - oversize proofs (black and red), 2p. (Mapcase 13V-F-05)
      - prospectus: printed copy (Box 21)
    - Venus and Adonis. Rochester, NY, Leo Hart, 1931.
      - book jacket: pencil draft (Box 21)
      - book jacket: ink and pencil draft (Box 21)
      - cover drawing: tempera draft (Box 21)
      - cover drawing: tempera sketch (Box 21)
      - title-page: pencil draft (Box 21)
      - p.31: pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 21)
      - p.31: ink sketch (Box 21)
      - p.39: pencil drafts (Box 21)
      - p.43: pencil draft (Box 21)
      - p.43 and 47: pencil drafts (Box 21)
      - p.47: pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 21)
      - p.51: ink and watercolor sketch (Box 21)
      - p.51: pencil draft (Box 21)
      - p.51: pencil sketch (Box 21)
      - p.59 and unused illus.: pencil drafts (Box 21)
      - p.63: pencil drafts (Box 21)
      - p.71: pencil drafts (Box 21)
      - p.75: pencil draft unused illus.: (Box 21)
      - ink and watercolor sketch (Box 21)
      - unused illus.: pencil and watercolor sketch (Box 21)
      - unused illus.: ink and watercolor drafts, 5p. (Box 21)
      - unused illus.: pencil draft (Box 21)
      - prospectus: printed leaflet (with related articles) (Box 21)
    - Venus and Adonis. Rochester, NY, Leo Hart, 1934.
      - prospectus: printed leaflet (Box 21)
  - Shephard, Esther
    - Paul Bunyan. New York, Harcourt Brace, [1941]
      - book jacket: pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 21)
      - frontispiece: oversize pencil drafts, 2p. (Mapcase 13V-F-05)
      - title-page: pencil drafts (Box 21)
      - p.3: pencil draft p.3: (Box 21)
      - oversize pencil draft (Mapcase 13V-F-05)
      - p.17: pencil draft (Box 21)
      - p.25: oversize pencil draft (Mapcase 13V-F-05)
      - p.37: pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 21)
      - p.37: oversize pencil drafts, 2p. (Mapcase 13V-F-05)
      - p.37 and 55: pencil drafts (Box 21)
      - p.55: oversize pencil draft (Mapcase 13V-F-05)
      - p.65: oversize pencil draft (Mapcase 13V-F-05)
      - p.65 and 73: pencil drafts (Box 21)
      - p.73: oversize pencil draft (Mapcase 13V-F-05)
      - p.85: oversize pencil draft (Mapcase 13V-F-05)
      - p.85 and 95: pencil drafts (Box 21)
      - p.95: oversize pencil draft (Mapcase 13V-F-05)
      - p.99, initials and type layout: pencil drafts, 6p. (Box 21)
      - p.105: pencil draft (Box 21)
      - p.105: oversize pencil draft (Mapcase 13V-F-05)
      - p.105 and 113: pencil drafts (Box 21)
      - p.113: oversize pencil draft (Mapcase 13V-F-05)
      - p.129: oversize pencil draft (Mapcase 13V-F-05)
      - p.129 and 137: pencil drafts (Box 21)
      - p.137: oversize pencil draft (Mapcase 13V-F-05)
      - p.153 and 161: pencil drafts (Box 21)
      - p.161: oversize pencil draft (Mapcase 13V-F-05)
      - p.175 and 185: pencil drafts (Box 21)
      - p.185: pencil draft (Box 21)
      - p.185: oversize pencil drafts (Mapcase 13V-F-05)
      - p.197: oversize pencil draft (Mapcase 13V-F-05)
      - p.197 and 209: pencil drafts (Box 21)
      - p.209: oversize pencil draft (Mapcase 13V-F-05)
      - p.217: oversize pencil draft (Mapcase 13V-F-05)
      - p.225: pencil draft (Box 21)
      - p.225: oversize pencil draft (Mapcase 13V-F-05)
      - illus. not used: pencil drafts, 3p. (Box 21)
      - misc. (Box 21)
  - Soule, Isobel Walker
    - The vigilantes hide behind the flag. [New York, International Labor Defense, 1939]
      - cover design: pencil draft (Box 21)
  - Squires, Frederick
    - Architec-tonics, the tales of Tom Thumbtack. New York, W.T. Comstock Co., 1914.
      - proofs, 36p. (Box 21)
  - Swift, Jonathan
    - Gulliver's travels (oversize). (not published)
      - pencil drafts (Box 21)
  - Thoreau, Henry David
    - On the duty of civil disobedience. New Haven, CT, Chorobates, 1928.
      - title-page vignette: ink drafts, 2p. (Box 21)
  - Tristan
    - The romance of Tristan and Iseult. (not published)
      - cover design: pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 21)
  - Untermeyer, Louis
    - [A poetry anthology for schools]
      - oversize charcoal and ink (black and green) draft for end-papers (Mapcase 13V-F-05)
      - oversize ink sketch for end-papers (Mapcase 13V-F-05)
  - Vercel, Roger
    - In sight of Eden. New York, Harcourt Brace {c1934]
      - heading for chapter one: pencil draft (Box 22)
  - Voltaire
    - Candide. New York, Random House, 1928
      - cover design: ink and pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 22)
      - cover design: ink sketch (Box 22)
      - title-page: pencil draft title-page: (Box 22)
      - pencil drafts, 2p. title-page: proof, 1p. (dated 1927) (Box 22)
      - initial letters: ink drafts, 7p. (Box 22)
      - initial letters: ink drafts (Box 22)
      - initial letters: ink lettering (À), 3p. (Box 22)
      - initial letters: pencil drafts, 7p. (Box 22)
      - initial letters: proofs (blue ink) (Box 22)
      - p.71: ink drafts, 1p. (Box 22)
      - suppressed illus.: ink drafts, 1p. (Box 22)
      - suppressed illus.: pencil draft, 1p. (Box 22)
      - suppressed illus.: proofs, 20 copies and one signed proof copy (Box 22)
      - suppressed illus.: see also: Adler, Elmer, t.l.s. to Rockwell Kent
      - suppressed illus.: see also: Book illus.: Nash, Ogden-Quartet...
      - ink drafts, 3p. proofs, mock-up pages (Box 22)
      - paper samples: 109p. (Box 22)
      - prospectus: printed leaflet (Box 22)
      - prospectus: printed leaflet, 4p. (with 3 watercolor illus.) (Box 22)
      - unbound set of hand-colored pages, 29 l. (Box 22)
      - printed misc., 2 items (Box 22)
    - Candide. New York, The Literary Guild, 1929
      - prospectus: printed leaflet, 2c. (Box 22)
    - Candide. Garden City, NY, Hanover House, 1959
      - book jacket: ink draft (Box 22)
      - book jacket: pencil drafts, 3p. (Box 22)
      - [Candide]: ink draft (Box 22)
      - [Candide]: pencil draft (Box 22)
      - [Candide, two figures, woman in doorway]: pencil drafts (Box 22)
      - [three figures]: ink sketch (Box 22)
      - [three figures]: pencil and ink draft (on sepia) (Box 22)
      - [three figures]: pencil draft (Box 22)
      - [two figures]: ink draft (Box 22)
      - [two figures]: pencil draft (Box 22)
      - [two figures]: pencil draft (on sepia) (Box 22)
      - [woman in doorway]: ink draft (black and white on sepia) (Box 22)
      - [woman in doorway]: ink draft (for one color plate) (Box 22)
      - [woman in doorway]: ink sketch (Box 22)
      - [woman in doorway]: pencil draft (Box 22)
      - misc. (Box 22)
  - Washburne, Heluiz Chandler
    - Land of the good shadows. New York, John Day, 1940
      - book jacket: pencil drafts, 4p. (Box 22)
      - book jacket: t.ms., 1p. (notes and one printed item) (Box 22)
  - We pledge peace: a friendship book. [San Francisco, American Russian Institute, 19--]
    - printed copy, 100p. (Box 22)
  - Wexley, John
    - The judgement of Julius and Ethel Rosenberg. New York, Cameron & Kahn, 1955.
      - book jacket: ink and pencil drafts (Box 22)
  - Whitman, Walt
    - Leaves of grass. New York, Heritage Press, 1936.
      - colophon: proof, 2p. (Box 22)
      - p.328: proof (Box 22)
      - pen-and-ink drawings, signed, with directions to printer (Box 22)
      - pencil drafts, 36p. (Box 22)
      - title-page, vignettes, illus. and colophon, 127p. (Box 22)
      - printed book, inscribed (Box 22)
      - misc. (Box 22)
  - Wilder, Thornton
    - The bridge of San Luis Rey. New York, Boni, 1929
      - cover design: pencil drafts, 4p. (Box 22)
      - cover design: watercolor drafts (blue and yellow), 3p. (Box 22)
      - cover design: oversize watercolor draft (many colors) (Box 22)
      - title-page: oversize pencil drafts (Mapcase 13V-F-05)
      - title-page: proof (Box 22)
      - p.[11]-proof: 3 copies (Box 22)
      - p.[19]-proof p.77: (Box 22)
      - proof (black ink) (Box 22)
      - p.77 and 109: oversize proof (blue ink) (Box 22)
      - proofs: on the verso of many drafts throughout the collection (Box 22)
    - The Cabala. (Designed for Charles Boni's "Paper book" series, but not published.)
      - book cover: pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 22)
      - book spine: ink and watercolor sketch (Box 22)
      - book spine: pencil drafts (Box 22)
      - lettering: pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 22)
- Series VII: Bookplates
  - A., C.: (Box 23)
    - proof (Box 23)
  - Abbott, Katherine:
    - ink draft (Box 23)
    - proof (Box 23)
  - Adler, Elmer:
    - pencil drafts, 3p. (Box 23)
    - proof (Box 23)
  - Albright Art Gallery (The Buffalo Fine Arts Academy) [1934]:
    - pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 23)
    - printed copies, 4p. (Box 23)
  - Allen, Arthur S., Jr.:
    - pencil sketch (Box 23)
    - printed copies, 2p. (Box 23)
  - Altschul, Arthur G.:
    - pencil draft (Box 23)
  - American Painters Sculptors:
    - pencil draft (Box 23)
  - Ancker, Lydia:
    - ink sketch (Box 23)
    - pencil drafts (Box 23)
  - Antioch Press (Yellow Springs, Ohio):
    - series of bookplates for general use: printed copies, 10p. (Box 23)
  - Armitage, Merle:
    - ink draft (Box 23)
    - pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 23)
    - printed copy. (Box 23)
    - See also: Titled drawings, etc.: The wanderer.
  - The Authors League of America:
    - pencil drafts, 3p. (Box 23)
    - proof (Box 23)
  - Avery, George Edwin:
    - pencil draft (Box 23)
  - Betterman, Henry Lewis, Jr.:
    - pencil draft of lettering (Box 23)
  - Becker, Leod Daw:
    - pencil drafts, 4p. (Box 23)
  - Block, George A., Jr.:
    - ink sketch pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 23)
    - pencil sketch (Box 23)
  - Borngman, Henry S.:
    - pencil draft (Box 23)
    - pencil sketch (Box 23)
    - proof (Box 23)
  - Bostedo, Gardner E.:
    - printed copies, 3p. (Box 23)
  - [Boy looking upward with dove flying out of his hand] (Box 23)
  - Briarcombe Farm:
    - ink sketch (Box 23)
  - Brush, Katharine:
    - pencil drafts, 4p. (Box 23)
    - printed copies, 2p. (Box 23)
  - Burne Jones, Dan. (Box 23)
  - C.:
    - ink draft (Box 23)
  - C.C.:
    - pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 23)
  - C., H.:
    - Proof (Box 23)
  - Camp Serenity:
    - pencil sketch (Box 23)
  - Cerf, Bennett A.:
    - pencil sketch, 4 (Box 23)
    - printed copies (Box 23)
  - Chapin, Roy Dikeman:
    - pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 23)
    - pencil and ink sketches, 2p. (Box 23)
  - Chicago Latin School:
    - ink sketch and pencil draft (Box 23)
    - pencil drafts (Box 23)
    - printed copy (2) (Box 23)
  - Church, Eleanor B.:
    - pencil draft (Box 23)
  - Clarke, Jeanette:
    - ink and pencil draft of lettering (Box 23)
    - See also: Bookplates: Printed misc.
  - Colish, A.:
    - ink and pencil draft (Box 23)
    - ink lettering (Box 23)
    - ink sketches, 2p. (Box 23)
    - pencil drafts, 12p. (Box 23)
  - College of Preachers (Washington DC):
    - pencil draft (Box 23)
    - pencil sketch (Box 23)
  - Corey, George Henry:
    - pencil drafts, 3p. (Box 23)
    - pencil sketch proofs, 2p. (Box 23)
  - Cranbrook Institute of Science (Bloomfield Hills, MI) [1936]:
    - ink lettering (Box 23)
    - pencil draft (Box 23)
    - proof (blue ink) (Box 23)
  - Cowdin, John Cheever:
    - ink draft, 1p. (Box 23)
  - Dahlgren, Olga Drexel:
    - printed copy (Box 23)
  - Dammann, Marjorie and Richard:
    - ink and pencil lettering (Box 23)
    - pencil drafts, 4p. (Box 23)
  - Denby, Charles and Rosamond:
    - 2 printed copies (Box 23)
  - Desjardins, Gregory T.:
    - pencil drafts, 3p. (Box 23)
    - pencil sketch (Box 23)
  - Doane, Gilbert H.:
    - pencil sketch (Box 23)
  - D.O.D. Dreher (Monroe F.) Inc.:
    - pencil sketches, 5p. (Box 23)
  - Drepperd, Carl W.:
    - pencil draft (Box 23)
    - pencil sketches, 2p. (Box 23)
  - E.M.:
    - pencil drafts, See: Bookplates: Gerald Kelly
  - Ehrich, Edward Price:
    - printed copy (Box 23)
  - Emmett, Burton:
    - pencil draft (Box 23)
    - pencil sketch (Box 23)
    - printed copy (Box 23)
  - Etnier, Stephen Morgan:
    - printed copy (Box 23)
  - Ewing, George R.M., Jr.:
    - printed copy (Box 23)
  - Friel, Helen Ottillie & John Whiting. Jesuit Seminary. [1957]:
    - pencil drafts of lettering (Box 23)
    - pencil sketch (Box 23)
  - Gellrer, H.M.:
    - ink sketch (Box 24)
    - ink tracing (Box 24)
    - pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 24)
    - proofs, 10p. (Box 24)
    - See also: Bookplates: printed misc. A.S.B.C.D.
  - Gillam, Burnes:
    - ink sketch (Box 24)
    - pencil and ink wash sketch (Box 24)
    - pencil drafts, 10p. (Box 24)
  - Greenland Press (Pittsburgh, PA):
    - ink draft (Box 24)
    - ink sketch (Box 24)
    - pencil drafts, 4p. (Box 24)
    - pencil sketches, 2p. (Box 24)
  - Greenland Press (Pittsburgh, PA): (Box 24)
    - See also: Bookplates: Snedden Memorial. Stanford Univ. Library: pencil draft
  - Greenland Press-series of bookplates for general use:
    - printed copies, 13p. (Box 24)
    - printed leaflet (Box 24)
    - proofs of second printing, 6p. (Box 24)
  - Green Tiger Press, La Jolla, CA:
    - printed copy. (Box 24)
    - 25 items in envelope (Box 24)
  - Grutman, D.:
    - pencil draft (Box 24)
    - pencil sketch (Box 24)
  - Hamershlag, Robert J.:
    - pencil draft (Box 24)
    - printed copy (Box 24)
  - Hart, Joan and Horace:
    - printed copy (Box 24)
    - tempera draft and sketch (Box 24)
    - See: Book illustration: Shakespeare: Venus and Adonis: cover drawing
  - Hart, Leo:
    - pencil drafts, 4p. (Box 24)
    - pencil sketch (Box 24)
    - printed copy (Box 24)
  - Harwell (À):
    - ink sketch (Box 24)
    - pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 24)
  - Harwell, Hazel and Richard:
    - pencil draft (Box 24)
    - proof (blue ink) (Box 24)
  - Hickey, Edward W.:
    - printed copy (Box 24)
  - Hinrichs, Marie Luise:
    - ink lettering (Box 24)
    - pencil draft (Box 24)
    - pencil sketch (Box 24)
    - proof, 3p. (Box 24)
  - Holgate, E. Josephine:
    - ink drafts (Box 24)
    - ink sketch (Box 24)
    - printed copy (Box 24)
  - Holt, Lucille:
    - pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 24)
  - Horwitt, Nathan G.:
    - pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 24)
    - 2 printed copies (Box 24)
  - Jackson, Joseph O.:
    - pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 24)
  - Jones, Jacqui & Dan Burne:
    - pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 24)
    - See also: Cataloged materials: Dan Burne Jones: bookplate
  - K., R.L.:
    - proof photograph of printed copy (Box 24)
  - Kelly, Gerald:
    - pencil drafts (Box 24)
    - proof (Box 24)
  - Kempner, Alan Horace:
    - pencil draft (Box 24)
    - printed copy (Box 24)
  - Kent, Barbara & Gordon:
    - ink and pencil drafts (Box 24)
  - Kent, Frances Lee and Rockwell:
    - printed copy (Box 24)
    - 2 copies (Box 24)
  - Kent, Kathleen Finney:
    - ink sketch (Box 24)
  - Kent, Gordon:
    - printed copy (Box 24)
  - Kent, Rockwell, III:
    - printed copy (Box 24)
  - Kent, Sally and Rockwell:
    - pencil drafts (Box 24)
  - Kimball, LeRoy Elwood:
    - pencil drafts, 2p.: (Box 24)
    - printed copy (Box 24)
  - King, Florence:
    - printed copy (Box 24)
  - Kingstree, South Carolina:
    - pencil draft (Box 24)
  - Kittredge, William A.:
    - printed copy (Box 24)
  - L., H.:
    - printed copy (Box 24)
  - L., N.:
    - Proof (Box 24)
  - Lambert, Emily Milliken:
    - pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 24)
  - Lambert, Marion L.J.:
    - pencil sketches, see: Bookplates: Mary Ryan Lang, Louise and Gilbert: printed copy (Box 24)
  - Lawrenceville School:
    - pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 24)
    - pencil sketches, 5p. (Box 24)
  - Levinson, Leonard R.:
    - pencil draft (Box 24)
  - The Library of Congress. Rare Book Collection:
    - pencil draft pencil sketch (Box 24)
    - ink draft of lettering (Box 24)
    - Lyon Memorial. University of Rochester Library:
    - pencil drafts, 3p. (Box 24)
  - McGuire, Harry:
    - pencil sketches, 2p. (Box 24)
  - Macy, Helen and George:
    - printed copies, 2p.: (Box 24)
    - pencil drafts, 1p. (Box 24)
  - Malinkrodt (Edward) Memorial. Harvard University:
    - pencil drafts, 3p. (Box 24)
  - Marcus, Billie and Stanley: (Box 24)
    - pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 24)
    - pencil sketch (Box 24)
  - Mendez, Albert Alexander:
    - pencil sketch (Box 24)
    - printed copy (Box 24)
  - Milburn, George:
    - Proof (Box 24)
  - Miller, Elizabeth:
    - Proof (Box 24)
  - Murphy, Ray Slater:
    - pencil and ink drafts, 2p. (Box 24)
    - printed copy (Box 24)
  - Neuman, J.B.:
    - pencil draft (Box 24)
  - O'Neil, Harry J.:
    - printed copy The Open Road: (Box 24)
    - See: Stationery: The Wayfarers Travel Agency
  - P., H.:
    - Proof (Box 24)
    - woodcut prints (Box 24)
  - Palmer, John R.:
    - pencil sketches, 2p. (Box 24)
    - printed coy (Box 24)
  - Pickering, Loring:
    - pencil draft (Box 24)
  - Prentiss, Samuel Loomis:
    - printed copy (Box 24)
  - Pulitzer, Ralph (À):
    - ink sketch (Box 24)
  - Pulitzer, Ralph:
    - pencil drafts (Box 24)
  - Pulitzer, Ralph and Margaret Leach:
    - pencil draft (Box 24)
    - printed copy (signed): (Box 24)
    - printed copies, 2p. (Box 24)
  - R.:
    - pencil sketch (Box 24)
  - R., G.:
    - ink sketch (Box 24)
  - R., H.:
    - pencil drafts (Box 24)
  - R., K.:
    - proofs, 2p. (Box 24)
  - R., L.:
    - pencil and ink drafts (Box 24)
  - R., P.:
    - ink sketch (Box 24)
    - proof (Box 24)
  - Rasmussen, A.C.:
    - ink sketch (Box 24)
  - Riggs, Austin:
    - pencil sketch (Box 24)
  - Rosen, Lucie:
    - Proof (Box 24)
  - Rosenberg, Anne:
    - printed copy 3 copies (Box 24)
  - Rosenblum, Arthur M.:
    - pencil drafts, 3p. (Box 24)
    - pencil sketches, 2p. (Box 24)
  - Ryan, Mary and Marion L.J. Lambert:
    - pencil sketches, 2p. (Box 24)
  - Sackett, Ruth Porter:
    - pencil sketches, 3p. (Box 25)
  - Sarnoff, Michael:
    - pencil sketch (Box 25)
  - Schreiber, George Gebner:
    - pencil draft (Box 25)
  - Schwarz, Charles:
    - pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 25)
  - Slemons, Anne and Morris:
    - pencil draft (Box 25)
  - Smith, John J.:
    - ink sketch (Box 25)
  - Snedden Memorial. Stanford University Library [1938]:
    - pencil and ink sketch (Box 25)
    - pencil drafts, 5p. (Box 25)
  - Southam, Gordon Hamilton:
    - pencil drafts, 3p. (Box 25)
  - Steinhardt, Maxwell:
    - pencil drafts and ink drafts, 3p. (Box 25)
    - printed copies, 2p.: (Box 25)
    - proof, 1p. (Box 25)
  - (Elnita) Straus Library:
    - pencil sketch (Box 25)
  - Sulzberger, Arthur Hays:
    - ink sketch (Box 25)
    - pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 25)
    - 12 copies (Box 25)
  - T., C.:
    - pencil draft (Box 25)
  - Tatum, George Bishop:
    - pencil drafts, 5p. (Box 25)
    - pencil sketch (Box 25)
  - (Louise Baldwin) Thompson Fund. Bangor Public Library:
    - pencil drafts (Box 25)
    - pencil sketch (Box 25)
  - W., E.:
    - 3 copies (Box 25)
  - Walker, Elmendorf:
    - ink sketch, 2p. (Box 25)
  - The Warner Library:
    - ink sketch (Box 25)
    - pencil drafts, 3p. (Box 25)
  - Wayhe, E.:
    - proofs, 2p. (Box 25)
  - Wheelwright, Mary C.:
    - pencil draft (Box 25)
    - printed copy (Box 25)
  - Whitmore, Frank H. [1934]:
    - pencil sketch (Box 25)
    - printed copy (Box 25)
  - Whitney, John Hay:
    - printed copy (Box 25)
  - Wilmerding, Lucius:
    - pencil draft (Box 25)
    - printed copy (Box 25)
  - Zigrosser, Carl:
    - proof (Box 25)
  - "Putzi;"
    - pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 25)
    - pencil sketch (Box 25)
  - [boy looking upward]:
    - ink draft (Box 25)
    - ink sketch (Box 25)
    - pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 25)
  - [medieval figure]:
    - ink and pencil draft (Box 25)
    - pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 25)
  - [nude looking upward]:
    - ink sketch (Box 25)
    - pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 25)
  - [sunrise in window]:
    - ink draft (Box 25)
    - pencil draft (Box 25)
  - [woman with lightning]:
    - pencil draft (Box 25)
  - Misc. ink and pencil drafts (Box 25)
  - Misc. ink draft (Box 25)
  - Misc. ink sketches, 5p. (Box 25)
  - Misc. pencil drafts, 45p. (Box 25)
  - Misc. pencil sketches, 4p. (Box 25)
  - Printed misc.:
    - American Society of Bookplate Collectors and Designers. (Box 25)
      - Year book 1969/1970. [Pasadena, CA.] the society, 1972. 26p.(Vol. 35):